Mr. 365 is a tv movie, romance film directed by Christie Will Wolf.
When workaholic reality TV producer Sophie starts working on a holiday-season show about Will, a wildly sexy guy who celebrates Christmas every day
of the year, she finds herself falling for her mysterious, unlikely new star, renewing her long-lost faith in Xmas in the process.
Sophia Worthy, played by Chelsea Hobbs.
Will, played by Christopher Russell.
Paul, played by Matthew Kevin Anderson.
Lindsey, played by Jill Morrison.
Fred, played by Ken Camroux-Taylor.
Aaron, played by Jeffrey C.R. Wallace.
The Very Excellent Mr.
Dundee  is a 2020 Australian comedy film directed by Dean Murphy, written by Robert Mond and Dean Murphy, and starring Paul Hogan, Rachael Carpani, Jacob Elordi,
Charlotte Stent, Nate Torrence, Chevy Chase, John Cleese, Olivia Newton-John, Reginald VelJohnson, Shane Jacobson, Wayne Knight and Kerry Armstrong.
Paul Hogan is reluctantly thrust back into the spotlight as he desperately
attempts to restore his sullied reputation on the eve of being knighted.
The title pays homage to Hogan's famous role of Crocodile Dundee.
It was released on Amazon Prime Video on 17 July 2020, and was the final
film Olivia Newton-John starred in before her death in 2022.
The film explores themes of based on novel or
book, television producer, christmas.
The tone is emotional.